<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>#StudentsAgainstCorona</title>
    <link>http://StudentsAgainstCorona.co.uk/</link>
    <description>Recent content on #StudentsAgainstCorona</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="http://StudentsAgainstCorona.co.uk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://StudentsAgainstCorona.co.uk/posts/1/01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://StudentsAgainstCorona.co.uk/posts/1/01/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://StudentsAgainstCorona.co.uk/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://StudentsAgainstCorona.co.uk/about/</guid>
      <description>Students in towns and cities across the world are coming together to help out the most vulnerable members of our communities affected by the Covid-19 crisis.
Whether it’s buying a carton of milk or walking the dog, there are simple tasks that people in isolation or at high-risk cannot perform on their own. We have a responsibility to both #flattenthecurve and take concrete action to lighten the burden on those most affected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Can I Help?</title>
      <link>http://StudentsAgainstCorona.co.uk/how_can_i_help/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://StudentsAgainstCorona.co.uk/how_can_i_help/</guid>
      <description>With universities having closed around the world, several full-time students now find themselves free. The vast majority also happen to belong to a relatively low-risk group.
There are several ways you can help vulnerable people in your community:
 Grabbing Groceries Walking Dogs Chatting Over the Phone And much more!  Follow Your Government’s Advice: It is vital that you adhere to the advice and measures that have been prescribed by your respective governments – washing your hands and social distancing are two simple examples.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Press</title>
      <link>http://StudentsAgainstCorona.co.uk/press/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://StudentsAgainstCorona.co.uk/press/</guid>
      <description>For press: we need coverage to spread the word about Corona virus!
Please send us an email here if you&amp;rsquo;d like to publish an article.
Latest news articles:
Cherwell - Oxford student founds Coronavirus help group
BBC - Coronavirus: Oxford University students set up help group
Oxford Mail - Students Against Coronavirus group to help isolated in Oxford
The Mercury - How Leicestershire is fighting back as coronavirus takes hold</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>